<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="Names">
        <item>Coin Magnet v1.0</item>
        <item>Coin Magnet v2.0</item>
        <item>Wallet</item>
        <item>Bigger Wallet</item>
        <item>Even Bigger Wallet</item>
        <item>Even Bigger Bigger Wallet</item>
        <item>Biggest Wallet</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Descriptions">
        <item>
            Tired of passing just out of range of those pesky, hard to reach coins?
            \nTHEN LOOK NO FURTHER!
            With this coin magnet you can reach coins from up to 30 metres away!!!
        </item>
        <item>
            Is your rusty old coin magnet still not reaching all the places you want it to?
            Are you tired of having to walk in random areas to get that last coin?
            \nTHEN BOY DO WE HAVE A DEAL FOR YOU!
            With this coin magnet you can reach coins from up to 35 metres away!!!
        </item>
        <item>
            Did you already deposit your 25 Coin limit only to find the coin of your dreams?
            Did trading it break your heart and made you wish there was some way to deposit just one more coin?
            \nWELL YOU\'RE IN LUCK FRIEND!
            With this new wallet with ONE extra pouch you can deposit a whopping 26 coins!
        </item>
        <item>
            Has the spirit of capitalism sunk its claws into you and 26 coins is no longer enough?
            Would you rather hoard your remaining coins than trade them to Barry for pocket change AGAIN?
            \nTHEN THIS IS THE WALLET FOR YOU!
            Now packing TWO extra pouches you can deposit 27 coins easily!
        </item>
        <item>
            Is the uneven amount of 27 really grating on your nerves?
            Would you rather it just rounded off to a more memorable number that\'s divisible by 2?
            \nTHEN HAVE NO FEAR!
            This new and improved wallet lets you deposit the 28 coins your even-number loving heart desires!
        </item>
        <item>
            Has that pesky capitalism spirit been whispering in your ear again?
            Have you plotted the graphs and seen how quickly this investment pays for itself?
            \nTHEN WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR YOU MONEY HUNGRY MANIAC?!?
            See your bank account sore as you deposit a grand total of 29 coins daily!
        </item>
        <item>
            Do I even need to read you the sales pitch?
            It\'s the biggest wallet. The end of the road you\'ve been walking since you bought your first wallet.
            The light at the end of the tunnel. Whoever said size doesn\'t matter hasn\'t seen this bad boy!
            \nCOME ON! BUY IT!
            \nYOU KNOW YOU WANT TO!
            Let your capitalist heart rest easy tonight and every night when you deposit a massive 30 coins a day!
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="Images">
        <item>@drawable/coin_magnet</item>  <!-- Icon made by https://freepik.com from www.flaticons.com-->
        <item>@drawable/coin_magnet2</item> <!-- Icon made by dDara from www.flaticons.com-->
        <item>@drawable/wallet</item>  <!-- Icon made by https://freepik.com from www.flaticons.com-->
        <item>@drawable/wallet1</item> <!-- Icon made by https://smashicons.com from www.flaticons.com-->
        <item>@drawable/wallet2</item> <!-- Icon made by https://freepik.com from www.flaticons.com-->
        <item>@drawable/wallet3</item> <!-- Icon made by Pixel Buddha from www.flaticons.com-->
        <item>@drawable/wallet4</item> <!-- Icon made by https://freepik.com from www.flaticons.com-->
    </array>
    <integer-array name="Costs">
        <item>15000</item>
        <item>25000</item>
        <item>10000</item>
        <item>15000</item>
        <item>20000</item>
        <item>25000</item>
        <item>30000</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>